Well, Russia will definitely
Ну до Приднестровья Россия точно
reach Transnistria so Let's put off Kiev about
дойдёт так Давайте отложим Киевско об
How will you reach Transnistria How are you
Как вы дойдёте до Приднестровья Как вы
going to reach Transnistria by
собираетесь дойти до Приднестровья из
sea in my opinion You are leaving Transnistria by sea
мором по-моему Вы из мором уходите от
Yes, you
Приднестровья Да вы от Херсона
have rolled back from Kherson Yes, there is no longer any talk of any landing on
откатились Да ни про какие там десант на
Odessa because
Одессу уже даже речь не идёт потому что
your fleet is already not even in Crimea but in
ваш флот уже стоит даже не в Крыму а а в
Novorossiysk ra Hello Good
Новороссийске ра Здраствуйте Добрый
evening, famous Ukrainian
вечер известный украинский
blogger Hello, unknown
блогер Здравствуйте неизвестный
Russian
российский
viewer How are you on the stream Yes, there are
зритель Как вы на стриме Да сейчас на
a lot of slackers watching you on the stream now
стриме много бездельников вас
2600 of the best people on the
2600 лучших людей
planet who have been bent And by the way,
планеты э кого загнули А кстати флажок у
your flag has changed, what is the connection with Well, the
вас сменился с чем связа
flag Well, the banner there as you like The fact is that
Ну флаг Ну Знамя там как хоти Дело в том
I conduct streams with different flags of
что я провожу стримы с разными флагами
countries that support
стран которые поддерживают
Ukraine
Украину
It is clear What are you talking about today except
Понятно О чём сегодня беседуете кроме
for Ukraine, so today about Russia for a
как об Украине так сегодня о России уже
long time now only about Russia for example, how do you
давно только о России например как вы
feel about the fact that today the
относитесь к тому что сегодня
territory of Russia was hit by American missiles in  Taganrog They
территория России в Таганроге
say we are fighting America on the
Говорят мы же воюем с Америкой на
territory of Ukraine, what's so surprising,
территории Украины что ж удивительно так
on the territory of Russia, Taganrog, Kursk
на территории России таганрок Курская
region Well, and on the territory of Russia, on the
область Ну и на территории России на
territory of Ukraine, so that's why it turns
территории Украины так вот да почему
out you can't
получается вы не можете с Америкой
fight America on the territory of America,
воевать на территории Америки большие
God forbid, if big countries start fighting among
страны не дай Бог начнут воевать между
themselves, it's better to do it somewhere else. They are already
собой лучше уж где-нибудь Так они же уже
fighting. America is shelling the territory of
воюют Америка обстреливает территорию
Russia, on the territory of Russia, well, Russia, on the
России на территории ну Россию на
territory of
территории
Russia, with Ukrainian hands, let's say, it's not
России украинскими руками скажем так
important, it's
неважно
shooting back. Well, you signed up for
отстреливает Ну вы же подписались под
this. So you, I mean, you are Russians.
это Так вы же я имею в виду вы россияне
Why are you losers? America is
Почему вы терпилы вас Америка
shelling you. And you can't even do anything to America.
обстреливает А вы Америке ничего не
Well, formally, the
можете даже сделать Ну формально
Ukrainians are shelling with American
обстреливают украинцы американскими
missiles, that's not the point, but American
ракетами суть не в том но американские
missiles. Like, American instructors.
ракеты да типа американские инструкторы
Or do you think some Ukrainian is
или вы думаете какой-то украинец их
launching them, intelligence data is giving everything.
запускает развед данные даёт все
Yes, I think the American hand is launched there.
Да я думаю рука американцев там запущена
Seriously,
серьёз
why can't Putin tell
почему почему Путин не может сказать
America? So if you don't take the
Америке Так если сейчас не заберёте мы
Cuban now, we will
кубинца будем с территорией кубы
shell your
обстреливать вашу
territory with the territory of Cuba. Well, because times have
территорию Ну потому что времена очень
changed a lot. Russia is not what it
сильно изменились Россия ведь не такая
used to be. The weight of Russia.
раньше вес России
Wow.
Ух
decreased That is, I understand correctly
уменьшился То есть я правильно понимаю
that not so much, not so much of course,
что не настолько не настолько конечно
as you would like That is, I
как бы хотелось вам То есть я правильно
understand correctly that Russia Now
понимаю что Россия Теперь ничего не
can do nothing
может сделать
and America will not do anything special to Russia
так и Америка ничего особо России не
Well, they will supply Ukraine with a missile and that's
сделает Ну поставят ракету Украине вот и
it, it will not go with tanks for the sake of
всё она же не пойдёт танками ради
Ukraine's independence, that's right, that's not the
самостийно Украины правильно ещё суть не
point The point is that, look, America
в том Суть в том что смотрите Америка да
gives Ukraine planes and missiles and with these missiles and
даёт Украине самолёты ракеты и этими
planes they directly take and
ракетами самолётами прям берут и
shell the territory of the Russian
обстреливают территорию Российской
Federation and they are already directly saying this about the
Федерации и прямо уже это говорят что с
red lines Well, I can't tell you for sure about the red lines,
линиями Ну насчёт красных линий я вам
this is such a thing, apparently a floating story
это такое дело плавающая видимо история
Well, in America's interests, as it were, to weaken
Ну в интересах Америки как бы ослабить
Russia, something is
Россию что-то
unclear Here, any hemorrhoid on the
непонятно Вот любой геморрой на
territory of Russia As I see, what is
территории России Как я смотрите то что
America's interest, America's interest, I
интерес Америки интерес Америки я
understand I don't understand why Russia
понимаю Я не понимаю зачем Россия не
can't give America anything in response
может ничего дать в ответ
Well, how do you
Америке ну а как вы себе это
imagine this To bomb Washington or
представляете Вашингтон бомбить чтоли
what to do I don't know Alaska at least
что делать я не знаю я Аляску хотя бы
large countries By the way, regarding the
большие страны Вот кстати по поводу
war Yes, how many times has there been in history a
войны Да сколько раз было в истории там
confrontation between the United States there
противостояние Соединённых Штатов там
Russia and the Soviet Union fought on
России и Советского Союза воевали на
different territories on foreign
разных на разных территориях на чужих
soil yeah Stop, stop  PP Yes, it is once and now they
коре да Стоп стоп ПП Да она раз а сейчас
are fighting on the territory of
воюют на территории
Russia again with the hands of Ukrainians it doesn't matter by
России опять же руками украинцев неважно
whose hands Russia has grown Will in Afghanistan
чми руками раше срос Воли в Афганистане
And now they are directly bombing the territory of
А теперь бом напрямую бомбят территорию
Russia Yes,
России
you are passing off wishful thinking as reality
да вы выдаёте желаемое за действительно
Maybe you want America to
Может вам и хочется чтобы Америка
bomb Russia Well, for now And who is bombing the
Бомбила Россию Ну пока А кто бомбит
Ukrainians And how do they launch That is, do you
украинцы А как они запускают То есть вы
really think that some
реально считаете что там какой-то
farmer Stepan is there Yes, or Petro, they were
хуторянин Степан да Или Петро их
imprisoned and taught to operate the AMM Yes, the
посадили научили АММ управлять Да
American CX is so
Американ СХ
you can imagine some
так выж так ти представляете каких-то
wild
там диких
Ukrainians I am so By the way, you are
украинцев яж так это Кстати вы говорите
not talking about me, so who is talking about Tarasov RI
не я го то кто получается про Тарасов ри
Who is launching these
Кто запускает эти
AMs under the guidance of Western
ам под руководством наверняка западных
instructors for sure Well, how under the guidance, that
инструкторов Ну как под руководством то
is, a Western instructor does all the calculations,
есть Западный инструктор всё расчёты
everything and so on, they give the coordinates and the
водит всё и так дальше дают координаты а
Ukrainians just press the button Yes,
украинцы только кнопочку нажимают Да
most likely Well, it is the Americans who are
скорее всего Ну так это американцы
shelling Well, at one time in Vietnam they shot
обстреливают Ну в своё время во Вьетнаме
down American planes like that in
сбивали американские самолёты так во
Vietnam And why, like, in Russia they don't
Вьетнаме А почему типа вот в России не
shoot down
сбивают ракеты
American missiles like that It has come to
американские вот Дошло до
this Well, how is this happening and there is a
такого Ну как так получается
war here  Surprise, it turns out that Russia
война тут Удивите получается что Россия
cannot give an answer not only to America, but
не может дать ответ не то что Америке А
even to some Poland or Finland, to
даже какой-то там Польше Финляндии
anyone. Why is the war going on on the
никому Зачем пока Война идёт на
territory of Ukraine, as it were, and
территории Украины как бы и
Russia, that's why Russia is a deputy. Why should Russia
России вот зачем Россия зам Зачем России
expand the conflict? That's why, so that
расширять конфликт Вот для чего чтобы
America doesn't interfere with
чтобы Америка не лезла на территорию
Russia's territory. Well, it doesn't interfere. Like it did,
России Ну она и не лезет выле как лез
Kursk region,
Курская область
Taganrok, Moscow, Engels, Saratov, they're shelling a lot,
таганрок Москва Энгельс Саратов куча
and they even occupied the Kursk region.
обстреливают и даже курскую область
Well, they're
вообще оккупировали Ну они же
not shelling from American territory. But from
обстреливают не с территории Америки А с
Ukrainian territory. That's right, once again it doesn't
территории Украины правильно ещё раз
matter. Well, formally, formally,
неважно Ну формально формально формально
it's Ukraine that's shelling. Look, if
обстрел ведёт Украина смотрите если если
I'm in the neighboring apartment. And they shoot
я да буду соседней квартиры Да стрелять
at you. So what will it matter to you from
по вам да то вам что будет важно из
which apartment or who's shooting. Well,
какой квартиры или кто стреляет Ну
everyday analogies don't really work in politics.
житейские аналогии в политике они особо
Yeah, I get it. Who is an electrician by
не работают Ага понял вы кто по
education?
образованию
I'm an electrician by education. I
электрик Я электрик по образованию по Я
just see that you know a lot about politics.
просто смо что вы очень в политике
What kind of ordinary chatterbox am I? I
шарите Да какой там я обычный Балабол я
pass the time in
коротаю время в
rubles. Tell me, I'm interested in how
рубля Расскажите мне вот интересно как
Russia is going to win against the
Россия собирается выиграть у
collective
коллективного
West. Oh, look,
Запада О как бы смотрите
you have one. You know, there's a Gordon. I do
у вас Знаете есть такой Гордон у
n't know. Well,  such a type of slippery
вас не знаю Ну такой типа скользкий
unpleasant I don't know And
неприятный не знаю И
what about
что
there is a video on the Internet
вот там есть ролик в интернете
And Gordon with Pozner whose
А Гордон с познером чей
Crimea
Крым
Well
Ну
Gordon was late rolled out there and he
Гордона позно раскатал там вот и он
said the following thing late for Russia
сказал следующую вещь поздно для России
this is an existential threat and for the West
это экзистенциальная угроза а для Запада
No this is there Natives are beating some
Нет это там Туземцы бьют какие-то
let's do without philosophy How Russia
давайте без философии Как Россия
is going to win Ukraine seize
собирается выиграть Украине захватить
Kyiv seize Lvov bomb
Киев захватить Львов разбомбить
Washington I think Ukraine will be divided and you
Вашингтон Я думаю Украину поделят и вы
will see it how you divide it in order to
это увидите как вы её поделите для того
divide Ukraine you need to seize
чтобы поделить Украину нужно захватить
Kiev For example, Syrian rebels
Киевом Вот например сирийские повстанцы
captured Damascus yes
захватили Дамаск да
ran away everything yes And how do you here Ukraine While
убежал всё да А как вы вот Украина Пока
you Kyiv You do not seize well No one will
вы Киев Не захватите ну Никто же не
surrender to you Well really it is not
будет вам сдаваться Ну правда не
necessary And how to seize Well to the
обязательно А как захватывать Ну до
Transnistrian brackets How will you reach
приднестровские скобки Как вы дойдёте до
Transnistria How are you going to reach
Приднестровья Как вы собираетесь дойти
Transnistria in the
до Приднестровья в
plague in my opinion You are leaving
мором по-моему Вы из мором уходите от
Transnistria from the plague Yes you have
Приднестровья Да вы от Херсона
rolled back from Kherson No there is no talk of landing on
откатились Да не какие там десант на
Odessa  it's not going because
Одессу уже даже речь не идёт потому что
your fleet is already not even in Crimea but in
ваш флот уже стоит даже не в Крыму а а в
Novorossiysk Yes in the
Новороссийске Да в самом
Transnistrian region itself, the fourteenth year,
приднестровской четырнадцатый год то
Ukraine has lost a lot of
Украина потеряла очень много
territory once again, we take the
территорий ещё раз ещё раз мы берём
starting point Yes, how did you start going
точку отчёта Да как вот вы начали идти
to Transnistria, yes, that is, 2022, you
на Приднестровье да то есть 2022 год вы
entered Kherson in the first days, yes When you,
зашли в первые дни в Херсон да Когда вы
like Hitler, attacked us without declaring war,
как Гитлер без объявления войны напали
yes then you were given a beating, they rolled
на нас да вот вам потом дали звездюлей
back You, yes, you were given a beating in the
откатились Вы да вам дали звездюлей в
Kharkov region, they have already given it in Kursk
Харьковской области уже дали в Курской
How do you want to get to Transnistria
Как вы хотите дойти до Приднестровья
If you cannot liberate your
Если вы не можете освободить свою
Kursk region from the Americans, I
курскую область от американцев я Я же
say, by attrition, fatigue, fatigue in
говорю измором усталость усталость на
Ukraine, so look, so it turns out, so
Украине так смотрите так так получается
you are we, we are taking you by attrition, you are
так вы это мы вас измором берём у вас
tired, you are tired, What is the situation with your
усталость у вас усталость Что у вас с
economy now, Ukraine is tired of
экономикой сейчас усталость Украин от
war, how much is your key rate Now
вой сколько у вас Ключевая ставка Сейчас
you asked me a question, wait, I'm not saying
вы задали мне вопрос подожди не я говорю
Look, Russians are tired of war Yes, it
Смотри усталость россиян от войны Да
is shown by social surveys Yes, Russians
показывается соц опросами Да россияне
damn tired of war already more than
капец устали от войны уже больше
half of those who are ready to
половины тех кто готовы на любых
finish in Russia under any conditions finish under
условиях закончить в России закончить на
any conditions Look at the Levada Center
любых условиях Посмотрите Левада центр
survey I will answer you come on Wait I
опрос Вам отвечу давай Подожди ещ раз
say again look we will take you from Moro
говорю смотри мы вас берм из Моро
collective hall Ukraine [ __ ]
коллективный зал Украина сри
live Ukraine's economy is supported by
пожи экономика Украины поддерживается
Western countries Britain Germany France Japan
западными странами Британия
USA and
Германия Франция Япония США и
many, many others yes Russia is not
много-много других да Россия не
supported by
поддерживается
anyone Russia is being strangled Russia is being strangled by
никем Россию душат Россию душат
sanctions Gazprom is deflating Yes already in
санкциями Газпром сдувается Да уже в
loss instead of
убыли вместо
profit allies something there in
прибыли союзники чтото там в
Syria was taken out of Africa this Syrian hub was
Сирии вынут из афри сирийский этот хаб
closed Yes little by little
закрыли Да понемножку понемножку
look
смотрите
first they hit the Crimean bridge then they hit the
сначала били по крымскому мосту потом
Kursk region they stupidly went
уже били по Курской области тупо зашли
there and said That's it now this is our land
туда и сказали Всё теперь это наша Земля
and you won't do anything to us Yes now the
и вы ничего нам не сделаете Да теперь
Americans are handing over missiles and Ukraine is
американцы передают ракеты и Украина
free Well how is Ukraine America
свободна Ну как Украина это ж Америка
you are just afraid to admit Yes it hits
просто вам страшно признать Да бьёт по
any points in the Russian Federation
любым точкам в Российской Федерации вот
today they took out the airfield in Taganrog Yes
сегодня вынесли аэродром в Таганроге Да
and warehouses And so on what will you do
и склады И так дальше что вы сделаете
nothing you are being taken out everything you do
ничего вас выносят вы всё что вы делаете
you are kickbacks that is you  knocked you out of Kyiv knocked
вы откаты то есть вас выбили из Киева
you out of Kherson from the Kharkov
вас выбили из Херсона из Харьковской
region from the Kursk region yes All of you from
области из Курской области да Всё вы из
the superpower which was the Soviet Union
сверхдержавы которым был Советский Союз
as a result of defeat in the Cold War
в результате поражения в холодной войне
defeat to the United States in you have
поражения соединённым штатам во вы
now turned into a laughing stock
превратили сейчас в смех
state all of you no one is afraid and everyone
державу всё вас никто не боится и все об
wipes their feet on you for example for
вас вытирают
example the USA wipes their
например США вытирает Украина вытирает
feet Ukraine wipes their feet Syrian rebels wipe their feet on you
ноги сирийские повстанцы вытирают вас
Yes take back your base you
ноги Да забирайте свою базу вым ничего
can't do anything to you belashki give me about
не можете сделать белашки дати по поводу
About Syria in the place of the Ukrainians I would
По поводу Сирии на месте украинцев я бы
not be happy Why Why Why Because
не радовался Почему Почему Почему Потому
if Russia withdraws its troops Well
что если Россия выведет свои войска Ну
where will it send them to Ukraine
куда она их направит на Украину
right what contingent is there what contingent of
правильно какой там контингент какой там
your troops Yes it doesn't matter what kind of what
контингент у вас войск Да неважно
important what contingent Yes the
какойто какой важно какой контингент Да
devil knows I do
Чёрт его знает я же Ско сколько
n't know how many armored vehicles and how many people are there that's
бронемашин и сколько людей там я не знаю
exactly yes that is one thing there
вот именно да то есть там одно дело это
were there to control some barefoot
были там контролировать каких-то босых
bogeymen in the desert Yes and another thing
бармалеев в пустыне Да а другое дело Это
Who are the Ukrainians since you read to you yes what is it
ж кто украинцы раз вам вы же читали да
Ukraine supplied drones to the rebels
что это Украина поставляла дроны
and drone operators, that is,
повстанцам и операторов Дронов то есть
Ukraine in Syria Yes, under the guise of the Barmaleys, it
Украина в Сирии Да под видом бармалеев
also carried out drone strikes on the positions of
тоже вела удары дронами по позициям
Russian troops and Assad's, that's all
российских войск и Асадов ских вот и всё
now Ukraine Yes, now in Syria, Siri, naha, it doesn't
теперь Украина Да тепер уо Сирии Сири
matter that there is chaos or chaos, everything is no longer there, everything is no longer there, Russia will not be there, Russia has
наха не всё равно что там хаос не хаос
lost Russia has
там не будет Россия потеряла Россия
lost Hao, no one
потеряла Хао всё это уже никого не
cares anymore, here you are, bloggers, like
интересует вот вы блогеры как любите
Zabava, you like to talk, but you don't like it,
Забава вот любите говорить а не любите
Syria will be taken under control by Turkey,
вот Сирию возьмут под контроль Турция
Israel and the USA In short,
Израиль и США Всё короче
Russia will lose its coasts,
Россия потеряет свои побережья вот
Tartus and chemical bases, because of this, the whole
Тартус и хим базы из-за этого посы вся
colonial policy in Africa, yes, that
колониальная политика в Африке да то
is, Russia will shrink to the level of a swamp 1
есть Россия сожмётся до уровня болота 1
there, 200 years or so, yes, that is, it's the
там 200 каких-то годов да то есть это
same as, look, the Soviet Union was driven out
также как смотри Советский Союз выбили
of East Germany, Yes, from Eastern
из Восточной Германии Да из Восточной
Europe, from Afghanistan, everywhere, yes And then
Европы из Афганистана всюду да А дальше
it fell apart, that's all, that is, what can
и он развалился вот и всё то есть что вы
you scare, which of the countries can you scare
кого вы можете напугать кого вы из стран
and what the Soviet Union
можете напугать и чем Советский Союз -
was an ideologist, a Zron country, that is,
это была идеологи Зро ная страна то есть
which
которая
was, yes, the Soviet Union  The Union was an ideologist Zrona
была да Советский Союз был идеологи Зро
country and the Russian
ная страна а Российская
Federation country I agree no And now
Федерация страна согласен нет А сейчас
we are the same as everyone else no how where are
мы такие же как все нет как где такие-то
all of
все
you However, Well, the Russian Federation Well, this is a
вы Однако ж Ну российской Феде Ну это
fact, everyone sees it, the fact is
факт это все видят
indisputable, there has been no one yet Who would have
факт неоспоримы не было ещ никто Кто бы
proven the opposite some time ago, what did you
доказал обратное некоторое время назад
tell me, cockroaches How, how is it there,
вы мне что сказали тараки Как как там
I How do you see how you
это я Как вы видите как вы нам нас
present us to us, unhappy, everyone is
представляете несчастны с вас все
laughing at you, I am laughing at you now Yes,
смеются я сейчас смеюсь с вас Да
what can you do, you are
вы что вы можете в
sitting in insignificant conditions, the doors In short, they were still
[__] условиях сидите двери Короче
painted Under the Soviet Union,
красились ещё При Советском Союзе
probably so, this is a basement Yes, that's right Yes, a
наверное так это подвал Да ж правильно
basement in the Soviet Union,
Да подвал в Советском Союзе подвал
for some reason, a basement is painted, but now
почему-то красится а теперь сейчас
people have to sit and breathe this
приходится людям сидеть и дышать этим
basement Yes, there is mold in such an unpainted one
подвальных Да таким не крашеным там
I don't work in the Hermitage, that's
грибок Я же не в Эрмитаже работаю
right, for some reason, in America they work in
правильно почему-то в Америке работают в
normal conditions And when you
нормальных условиях А у вас когда в
built a basement in the Soviet Union, everything was
Советском Союзе подвал строили было всё
painted And now everything is damp Yes, why, and I'll
покрашено А теперь всё сыро Да почему а
explain, just don't interrupt me
объясню только вы меня не перебивайте
Let's have the same electrician in the same
Давайте такой же электрик на такой же
position in
должности на
Ukraine, in not the best conditions
Украине ни в чуть не лучших условиях ещ
again  Look, don't tell me about
раз Смотри ты мне не рассказывай про
Ukraine, we are leveling to the West, we are entering
Украину мы ровняем на запад Мы входим
again, look, you are real, that is, you,
в ещё раз Смотри ты реально То есть ты
Ukraine is not a superpower, pony, I am saying
мы Украина не сверхдержава пони я говорю
that you are not a superpower, you are a
что вы не сверхдержава вы
laughing power, which means that Russia is a laughing
смехдержава значит что Россия смех
power, come on, tell me, well, how much more do
держава давай скажи ну с чего же сколько
you still get, sitting in this
ты ещё получаешь Сидя в этом
kennel, well, the salary is a little good but
конуре Ну немного зарплата хорошая но
small, well, how much do I earn,
маленькая Ну сколько зарабатываю я
70,000, you sit in the basement for 700 dollars
70.000 ты за 700 долларов сидишь в
and breathe in this fungus, yes, I have a
подвале и дышишь этим грибком Да у меня
job for three days a day,
работа сутки
I am telling you, the same, and I went to see how
трое я вам говорю такой же и пошёл на
miserable they are, Hello, how is it,
какие они несчастные Здравствуйте как же
Tukha, you
Туха у вас грибы
open your mushrooms, olives, olives, yes, open them
открываете оливки оливки да да приоткрой
a little, horseshoes, with a
чуть-чуть подковы
knife, there is
ножиком
nowhere to put them, what are you doing there, how is your
много некуда девать что вы там Как ваша
life, in general, haven't you
жизнь вообще вилка не
tried a fork? I will be alone, so it's too early for me, let alone alone,
пробовали Я же один буду поэтому мне ВС
then you are everywhere with these hands,
не то что один Вы же потом этими руками
and my hands are clean, I washed these hands, they did
всюду А у меня руки чистые Я помыл эти
n't steal anything, I mean, you
руки ничего не крали я имею в виду вы
touch all the stains with these hands,
этими руками потом трогаете все пятна
and not me  I touch only everything except
а не я трогаю только всё кроме
clothes I understand what you are talking about politics
одежды понял о чём общаетесь о политике
war in Ukraine and Russia and there is a war
войне в Украине и России а есть война
Of course there is I know that there is a war no
Конечно есть Я знаю что сво есть войну
one
никто не
declared it well with
объявлял ну с
everyone calling it like Hot No this is not a
каждый называет как Хот Нет это не война
war no one declared it if there
никто войну не объявлял если бы война
was a war already NATO would have bombed your Russia
была уже б НАТО разбомбил вашу Россию
All I am saying is that everyone calls it what they
Всё я же говорю каждый называет её как
want but no matter what you call it people die
хочет но как её не назови люди погибают
every day Well people die in
каждый день Ну так люди погибают и в
fires like but this is not a war Well
пожарах типа но это же не война Ну так
people die simply because some
люди погибают просто потому что какие-то
people did not solve something some
люди что-то не не решили какие-то
issues this is a special military
вопросы это идёт специальная военная
operation you have your own we have ATO and no
операция у вас сво у нас ато а войны
one
никто не
declared war What difference does it make no one
объявлял Да какая разница никто не
declared it or declared it anyway martial
объявлял или объявлял всё равно военное
law exists you know where martial law does not exist in Russia
положение существует зна где у в России
Well how is
не существует военного положения Ну как
this a border in Russia
это гранич тер в России не введено
martial
военное
law has not been introduced partially introduced no regime Who
положение частично введено нет режим Кто
introduced you have a counter-terrorist
введён у вас контртеррористической
operation well from my understanding
операции ну э с моей с моего понимания
this is actually the same thing No this is not the
это фактически одно и тоже Нет это не
same thing no this is clearly in the
одно и то же нет это чётко есть в
legislation of Russia and there is a clear
законодательстве России так и чёткое
distinction between the regime of
разграничение режима
a counter-terrorist operation and the regime of
контртеррористической операции и режима
martial law  Let them decide so
военного состояния Пускай они решают так
I decided differently for myself This is my
я для себя решил по-другому Это моё
personal opinion You can decide that the Earth is
личное мнение Вы можете решить что Земля
square, for example, and what does your opinion
квадратная например ну и что ваше мнение
influence, so I decided it myself for myself, you
влияет так я его решил сам для себя
understand, and for yourself, so keep it for yourself
понимаете а для себя так держите для
Why are you doing
себя зачем вы
this? Keep the Earth for yourself And I do
это вы землю себе оставить А мне Земля
nt need the Earth, I need what my opinion is
не нужна мне нужна то что мнение какое я
and thats it, think your opinion
думаю и всё так думайте своё мнение
Keep it to yourself If anyone is interested in your
Оставьте при себе кому интересно ваше
opinion Well, youre communicating with me, I can
мнение Ну вы же со мной общаетесь я могу
tell you everything I want, so I dont
вам высказать всё что я хочу так мне не
need you to tell me that everything
нужно чтобы вы мне высказывали что всё
you want I
что вы
need for us to communicate on
хотите мне нужно чтобы Мы пообщались на
generally accepted facts and not some of your
общепринятых фактах а не какие-то ваши
fantasies Well, whats going on? Whats going on, lets
фантазии Ну а что происходит А что
say, in Ukraine now?
происходит допустим в Украине сейчас вот
Tell me, its not a war, but whats
расскажите что не война а что там
going on there No, its not a war, whats going on there is a
происходит Нет не война что там
special military operation to
происходит специальная военная операция
demilitarize the Russian Federation, an
по демилитаризации Российской Федерации
operation from a war Yes, the thing is that
операция от войны Да дело в том что
Ukraine is fighting and NATO is not fighting at full
Украина воюет и НАТО воюет не в полную
strength, that is, with a limited
силу то есть ограниченным контингентом
NATO contingent, tell me Whats the difference between a
НАТО вы мне Расскажите Чем отличается
war Im telling you Because if there
война Я же говорю Потому что если бы
was a war, we would have immediately bombed Moscow,
война была мы бы сразу разбомбили Москву
Leningrad, Rostov, Krasnodar Yes, but
Ленинград Ростов Краснодар Да Во а так
we immediately  I asked you a specific question
мы сразу я вам конкретный вопрос задал
What is the difference between the concept of war and a
Чем отличается понятие война От
terrorist operation Because
террористической операции Потому что
if war were declared, war is more
если бы объявили войну война - это более
full-scale, then they would bomb Moscow, St.
полномасштабная тогда бомбят Москву
Petersburg, Krasnodar, Rostov, you
Питер Краснодар Ростов
see, that's why Putin is afraid to declare
понимаете поэтому Путин боится объявить
war because he knows that
войну потому что знает что сразу же
Zelensky will immediately give a decree and Moscow will be bombed right away So what Well, that's
Зеленский даёт указ и сразу бомбят
why it's not a
Москву Ну и что Ну вот поэтому это не
war
война
now, well Okay Okay Who in your
сейчас ну О'кей Хорошо Кто в вашем
understanding is to blame, who is right and how to
понимании виноват кто прав и как это
resolve this, so it's all clear, like
решить так это всё понятно типа виновата
Russia is to blame, Ukraine is right And which side do you
Россия права Украина А вы какую сторону
represent? I represent the United
представляете Я представляю Соединённые
States of America I come from Rostov, I've been
Штаты Америки я родом родом из Ростова
living in California for 18 years, in 2
на 18 лет уже живу в Калифорнии через 2
years I will have my passport I'm already a
года будут чки Я уже гражданин
US citizen Yeah That is, roughly speaking, if we take it that way,
США Ага То есть грубо говоря если так
you betrayed your state
взять вы предали своё государство
Why Well because now in your
почему Ну потому что сейчас в вашей
country they are fighting
стране
for their own people, you
идёт за ших же тей
left 20 years ago, which means you had a
с 20 лет назад уехали значит у вас был
Russian passport and what Well, that means you are a
русский паспорт и что Ну значит вы
citizen of Russia, which means you betrayed your
гражданин России значит вы предался от
Russian citizenship Yes, I
российского гражданства Да я в
fully completed the exit process at the embassy 5
посольство оформил полностью выход ещё 5
years ago, I don't have Russian citizenship Yes,
лет назад нет российского гражданства Да
I moved to the
я 18 лет переехал в
USA at 18, about 13 years ago I received
США 13 лет где-то назад получил
US citizenship somewhere  and began the process of leaving
гражданство США и начал процесс выхода
Russian citizenship Yes, so that there is no
из российского гражданства Да чтоб не
double, so that there is no
двойного чтоб не было
double Russia Russian
двойного Росси российское
legislation allows it
законодательство разрешает воно
Citizenship more than once No, it does not allow
Гражданство не раз Нет не разрешает
Russian does not allow it simply there is no
Российское не разрешает просто нету
sanction for dual citizenship, that is,
санкции за двойное гражданство то есть
there is no punishment, but they do not allow
нету наказания но не разрешают в России
single citizenship in Russia half half
единое гражданство половина половина
thinking as far as I know I again Go
думая насколько я знаю я ещё раз Го
look so in Russia Look E in Russia
смотрите так в России Смотри Е в России
citizenship is one, it is impossible to have dual Yes but
гражданство одно нельзя двойного Да но
there is no
нету не
citizenship that's it that way it is not in one there
гражданства вот так так оно не в одной
may be
может быть
criminality in Colombia it is like it is forbidden to
криминалитет в Колумбии типа запрещено
have a second citizenship yes And we
иметь второе гражданство да А мы имеем в
mean yes Let's do more Yes, here in Japan If
виду да Давайте ещё Да вот в Японии Если
you become a citizen of another country
вы встаёте гражданином другой страны у
you are given about 2 years to leave that
вас даётся около 2 лет на выход из того
citizenship too well to leave But no But
гражданства тоже ну на выход Но не Но
it is not criminal That is, if you have
это не уголовно То есть если у вас есть
double n not sa there is there is in Japan there is a
двойной н не са есть есть в в Японии
punishment for this yes criminal yes that
есть за это наказание да уголовное да то
is garden prison or something Or I know not
есть сад тюрьму или что Или я зна не не
criminal - it is not always prison
уголовное - это не всегда тюрьма
criminal there may be a fine Yes
уголовная может быть штраф Да
and a criminal offense is listed for you
и числится за вами уголовное
if later repeated yes for
преступление если потом повторно да
example  then well okay I understand I
например тогда уже ну О'кей я Поня я по
don't know of any precedents for being put in jail for dual citizenship but I don't know
За двойное гражданство я не знаю но то
that persecution exists in some
что преследование есть в некоторых
countries Yes that's for
странах Да это
sure and where are you from
точно а вы
I'm from
откуда я откуда С
Transnistria That's where
Приднестровья Это
Moldova is Yes I
Молдавия Да
understand Teraspol you know such a city
понял терасполь знаете такой город
Tiraspol Tiraspol Tiras is the Dniester I think it was
Тирасполь Тирасполь тирас это Днестр
called that way
Вроде так назывался
once somewhere on the
когда-то где-то на
Dniester near Odessa Ukraine I understand And that's
Днестре возле Одес Украины понял А это
there And that's all I understand it's
там А всё я понял это там
where E in short there was some kind of war or
где Э короче там война была какая-то или
what that part of it is not controlled by
что что там часть не контролируется
Moldova
Молдовой
Well if you look at the map it's a
ну если Вы посмотрите по карте оно
bit of a state It looks like the country of
немножко государство Похоже как страна
Chile That's the line to enter from
Чили Вот такая линия чтобы заехать со
Moldova or
стороны Молдавии или
from Transnistria you need to You need to
со стороны Приднестровья вам нужно Вам
go through the border checkpoint yours
нужно пройти пограничный пункт ваш
must have documents that you live either
должны быть документы что вы живёте либо
there Tourist Well in short a bit of a pain in the ass And
там Турист Ну короче геморрой немножко А
what's your
как вас
name Sergey Sergey understood me
зовут Сергей Сергей понял меня
T citizenship now I'm thinking about making the fourth
Т гражданства сечас вот четвёртое думаю
And what are your three citizenships
делать А какие три гражданства у вас
Ukrainian Russian and Transnistrian
украинская Российская и Приднестровская
And how did you get Ukrainian Russian
А как вы украинская российское получили
in  this is Moldova in
в это Молдове в
Transnistria Ukraine here and Russians
приднестровьем Украине вот а россий у
each have Russian citizenship Pridnestrovie
каждого есть росе гражданство прид
Ukrainian received this where did you
украинско получили это где вы его
get it there in
получали там в
Moldova in Odessa Well yes And on what
Молдове в Одессе Ну да А на каком
basis did you come from another country
основании вы приехали из другой страны
what on the basis that Well
какм на основании того что Ну вот
look
смотрите
let's say If you If you let's say you are from
допустим Если вы Если вы допустим
Odessa yes you have every right to
Одессит да у вас есть полное право
apply for Ukrainian
подать документы на нское
citizenship sae you were born on the
гражданство сае вы родились на
territory of Transnistria You can
территории Приднестровья Вы можете
get both a Ukrainian passport and a
получить и украинской паспорт и
Moldovan one since Transnistria is
молдавский так как Приднестровье
considered part of Moldova And if you
считается часть Молдавии А если у вас
have a Moldovan one then you
есть молдавская то вы автоматически
can automatically get a Romanian one Well in short everyone
можете получить румынское Ну короче все
who lives in Transnistria they, roughly
кто живут в Приднестровье они как грубо
speaking, won the
говоря выиграли
jackpot with
джекпот с
citizenships only they didn't win from the
гражданствами только не выиграли с
territory yes
территории да
like well you know people are
типа ну знаете людей как бы
both satisfied and not satisfied you know that
и устраивает и не устраивает знаете то
is if you need to earn money somewhere you
есть если надо куда-то заработать денег
get a Romanian passport and go if let
румынский паспорт получил и погнал если
's say you need to go there for groceries
допустим нужно там за продуктами
in Ukraine please well that is
съездить в Украину пожалуйста ну то есть
Show the covers of these three pos I don't believe
Покажите обложки этих трёх пос Я не верю
that a person can have three passports
что может у человека быт три паспорта
this  some kind of
это какой-то
[ __ ] I won't show you why are you collecting
гон не покажу зачем вам это вы собираете
some information about me that's not right don't
информацию какую-то обо мне не так не
show it just with covers
показывайте это просто обложками вот
show that there are three passports I don't believe I won't
покажи что есть три паспорта я не верю
show Don't show And this was all invented
не покажу Не покаж А это придумали всё
Well let it be so And why do you need it I
это Ну пускай так будет А зачем вам не я
just can't understand you just have an
просто не могу понять у вас просто
American passport Well no I just do
американский паспорт вот Ну не я просто
n't believe you say that you live there And
не верю вы говорите что вы там живёте И
you were given a bunch of other countries in that country
вам в той стране выдали ещё куча разных
not that you went to those countries
стран не то чтобы вы уехали в те страны
but just there on the
а просто там на
spot why is this a bunch you call
месте почему это куча вы называете
Ukraine Moldova is a bunch or what Well at
Украина Молдавия это куча или что Ну
least plus two Passports you have Well well
минимум плюс два Паспорта у вас Да ну
look if you doubt
смотрите если вы допустим сомневаетесь в
MTO Look at the information this is
мто Посмотрите информацию это
publicly available on the Internet how do citizens of
общедоступная в интернете как граждане
Transnistria have several passports did
Приднестровья имеют несколько паспортов
you even know in what year did you
вы вообще знали хо в каком году Вы
receive these Ukrainian and Moldovan
получили вот эти украинский и молдавский
passports and Russian Ukrainian I received them in
паспорт и русский украинский Я получил в
2000 seventeen
2000 семнадцатом
and Moldovan Well as soon as I turned 16 I
а молдавский Ну сразу как 16 исполнилось
immediately received Moldovan and how do these
сразу молдавский получил а как эти
Moldovan and Ukrainian passports
молдавские и украинские паспорта
look like this you tell me something else
выглядят так вы меня что-то другое с
other you ask me what color is
другое спрашиваете меня какой цвет
good What color am I just naked now
хорошо Какой цвет я сейчас просто нагу
What color is a Moldovan Ukrainian passport
Какой цвет молдавской украинский паспорт
What color am I on Google
Какой цвет Я сейчас на Гугли вы меня
now do you want to provoke me to ask some
сейчас хотите спровоцировать на какие-то
questions or
вопросы или
what do you see You You come in You
что вот вы видите Вы Вы заходите Вы
come in from the other side you ask me now
заходите с другой стороны вы меня сейчас
one thing then another do you think
спрашиваете одно потом другое вы думаете
I will answer you everything No of course why do you
я вам всё буду отвечать Нет конечно с
mean you deceived my un you
чего значит вы обмани ун мой по вы
initially asked me to show then
изначально меня спросили показать потом
you ask me to open now you
вы попросите меня открыть теперь Вы меня
ask me what do you have what
спрашиваете какие у
accompanies this do you think I
вас что этому сопутствует вы думаете я
what or what Okay Let's do So how do the
что или что Хорошо Давайте Так по
sizes differ between the Ukrainian and Moldovan passports For
размерам насколько украинский паспорт и
example, how do
молдов ский отличаются Например
I know Well so You have both Well yes yes
я откуда знаю Ну так У вас же есть и тот
they are the same
и тот Ну есть да да одинаковые они
okay you got busted in Ukraine since 2016 they do
ладно ты спалился в Украине с 2016 года
not issue passports booklets an ID
не выдают паспорт книжечки выдаётся ID
card is issued Okay let it be so let's do it
карта Ну окей пускай будет так
Hello and what do you communicate with Yes
давай Здравствуйте а чём общаешься
just came in while there is nothing to talk about just
Да так просто зашёл пока не о чём
now I was talking with the boys from Crimea
вот сейчас с мальчишками с Крыма
young I am yes Well yes
молоды я да Ну да
some kind of military man It's cool and what do you communicate with
какой-то Прикольно а чём общаетесь
here on any topic on
тут на любые темы на
what Well just  talk to
какие Ну просто поговорить с
people for example I
людьми например
don't support some main topic Well
не поддерживаю основной какой-то темы Ну
just look my name is Vladimir And what about
просто вот меня Владимир вообще звать А
you
вас
My name is Andrey Well you see
как Меня Андрей зовут ну вот видите у
you have Andrey And where are you from Andrey city
вас Андрей А вы откуда Андрей город
meniscus And
мениски А
you I am Pskov
вы я Псков
Russia understood
Россия понял
Paratrooper Well why do you need to know this I wonder well no
Десантник Ну зачем вам это знать
need No why There are not
интересно ну не надо Нет почему Там не
only paratroopers in Pskov Well And what do you
только десантники же во Пскове Ну А кем
work as during the war What do you work as
работаете военной время Кем работаю
Yes
Да
machine gunner Yes seriously you are a military man
пулемётчик да серьёзно то вы военный
Seriously
серьёзно
machine gunner Ilya day of people for
пулемётчик Илю день людей за
money I for money people Yes
деньги я за деньги людей да
in principle no there was no such thing that a
в принципе нет не было такого чтобы
person would just come up and pay
просто человек подошёл заплатил
I don't
Я не
know Well it turns out you come out Yes
знаю Ну получается вы выходит да
what went for money people in Ukraine like that Well how to
что пошли за деньги людей в Украине
understand it turns out that's how a
так Ну как понять получается так
conflict begins he is obliged to
начинается конфликт он обязан
go occupier you are an occupier Oh come on
идти оккупант вы оккупант Ой ну давай
uncle Well come on why are you come on like that you are a contract
дядь Ну ну зачем ты давай так ты
soldier contract soldier when did you sign a
контрактник контрактник когда Подписал
contract in twenty-second in twenty-
контракт в двадцать втором в двадцать
second year after the start of the war yes
втором году после начала сво
before him before him Okay
да до него до него Хорошо
look You are not obliged to carry out
смотри Ты же не обязан исполнять
criminal
преступные
orders You must by law carry out
приказы Ты должен по закону исполнить
then appeal no Okay come on
потом обжаловать нет Хорошо давай так
if they tell you a little girl you  you
если тебе скажут маленькую девочку ты
will execute and then you will
исполнишь а потом будешь
appeal And what about little girls you have
обжаловать А что маленьких девочек у вас
Well I I ask you say that you need to
Ну я Я спрашиваю ты говоришь что нужно
execute and then appeal I ask
исполнить потом обжаловать Я спрашиваю
Yes if
Да если
you Well you give
тебе Ну ты приводишь
Which one And you see you see That is So it
Какую А видишь видишь То есть Значит
turns out that it is not always necessary to first
получается не всегда надо сначала
do and then appeal True Well so
сделать а потом обжаловать Правда Ну так
some kind of downright ridiculous
какой-то вообще прямо нелепый девочку
little girl No well there are scumbags who
маленькую Не ну есть Отморозки которым
on little girls Well let's do it this way uh then you
на маленьких девочек Ну давай так ээ то
know without freaks let's do it this way uh a military man there are the
зна без уродов давай так то ээ военный
same freaks explain Russian
такие же уроды есть объясни российский
Come on tell me a Russian military man must
Давай скажи российский военный должен
unquestioningly execute an order and
беспрекословно исполнять приказ
then appeal or still if the
потом е обжаловать либо вс-таки если
order is criminal he may not
приказ Преступный он может его не
execute it Yes we do not have criminal
выполнять Да у нас нету преступных
orders But if they give a criminal order
приказов Но если дают Преступный приказ
you may not execute it I
ты можешь его не выполнить я тебе ещё
repeat to you once again we do not have criminal orders
раз повторяю у нас нету преступных прика
I ask can a Russian military man
Я спрашиваю может ли российский военный
not execute an order if he believes that the
не исполнять приказ если он считает что
order is
приказ
criminal look how to understand
Преступный смотри как понять
Criminal Well
Преступный Ну
we understand This is wrong This is
наме понима Это неправильно Это
illegal this is how they tell you
противозаконно это так вот тебе говорят
Yes for example this woman because  that she is a
Да например эту женщину потому что она
spy Well, look, my friend, there is a
шпионка Ну как бы смотри дружище есть но
court that issues a verdict that she is a spy, she is not a
суд который выносит вердикт шпион она не
spy, you detain her, hand her over to those
шпион ты задерживаешь её отдаёшь в те
places where they sort things out, I understand Yes,
места куда там разбирается я понимаю Да
that is how it is necessary Yes, but imagine that, for
это ж так нужно Да а вот Представь что
example, you go into a village Yes, there is a
например ты Вы заходите в село Да там
woman there and the commander tells you, so
есть женщина и тебе командир говорит так
she is a criminal, she is ordered to
она преступница ей приказ
shoot, shoots
Расстрелять стреляет
someone Of course, I am, what are you saying, my friend That
какого-то Конечно я ну ты что дружище То
is, you are just a woman Yes, look, if a
есть ты просто женщина Да смотри если
woman comes out with a machine gun and starts
женщина выходит с автоматом начинает
shooting at someone, puts down a guy, of
стрелять в кого-то ложит пацана
course, they brought the woman and said that
конечно привели женщину да сказали что
she was captured because she was there A
её схватили потому что она там
spy And so on and your
Разведчица И так дальше и твой
commander sentenced her to be shot, he tells
командир приговорил её к расстрелу
you, he tells you, Shoot her, my
говорит тебе говорит Расстреляй её
friend, I
ты дружище я тебе ещё раз
repeat to you once again, there is a court for this in the Russian
повторяю есть для этого в Российской
Federation that
Федерации
issues a
суд который выносит
verdict for this
вердикт этой
woman Well, we dont have a firing
женщине Ну расстрела у нас нету я тея
squad, I will upset you again, lets
огорчу ещё раз давай
strain your brain like this Thats the whole point, no,
напрягает Вот и вся сущность нене
first they
сначала
appeal a deal with their conscience, I am a
обжалуются сделку со своей совестью я
simple person, I am a simple soldier I am
простой человек я простой солдат Я
carrying out an order, they will give an order tomorrow,
исполняю приказ те завтра дадут прика
just business And then I pressed  No, you are
растре просто дела А потом жал Нет ты
also responsible because
несёшь тоже ответственность потому что
no one should carry out criminal
никто не должен исполнять преступные
orders and that's all there is to it. A
приказы так и всё сво это есть
criminal order to unleash an
Преступный приказ по развязыванию
aggressive war is in this, there is a corresponding article in the
агрессивной войны в этом есть в
Criminal Code of the Russian Federation
Уголовном кодексе Российской Федерации
and all of these
есть статья соответствующая и все эти
are criminals, all of these Russian
есть преступниками все эти российские
military personnel. Yes, those who are fighting against Ukraine
военные Да которые воют против Украины
are
это
criminals even under Russian
преступники даже по Российскому
law. But since Russia is not a
законодательству Но поскольку Россия не
state governed by the rule of law, there, uh, the
правовое государство там
Constitution and laws are just
ээ Конституция и законы - это просто
fiction, there is
фикция там
only one president,
действует едино начале президента по
essentially the king, their emperor, that's all,
сути царя ихнего императора вот и всё
they are all disenfranchised
они все бесправные
slaves. Like, squeak, comment. Let's move on. Write
рабы лайк писка комент Идем дальше пись
to my Telegram right now. The axis is wine, and the
на мий Telegram прям зараз ось вин а
pope is very important. YouTube is
попк це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
driving us through Scar George's ban and I don't
загоняя нас через Скар Геор твый бан и
show people a lot of videos. I don't show people
дуже багато вдео не показую людям вчасно
information about streams at times,
не показуе информация про стримы тому
so that we can quickly
для того щоб ми Мали оперативный звязок
write to them and while there are videos in Telegram, OKM is also very
пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в телегра
important.  interesting and useful
окм вдео ще теж цикава и корисна
information and we are obliged to you for the
информация и ми повинни з вами трима
constant operational connection
постийний оперативный звязок
independently in that che will show you about This
незалежно в того чи покаже вам про Цей
YouTube Glory to Ukraine subscribe
YouTube Слава Украине подпишись